{
    "id": "1409b08356bf44e9a3086a0367cbdda7",
    "title": "Kinds of Sentences",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Please leave your footwear outside.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2b8976bb872845c4bdf5f81de7fca7e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you wait here?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b8bc98027b8a42168abef45c367b0935"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where have you been all this while?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "50ff0bd513a744c882de8d83759b29b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "We will not tolerate this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "698fe1da03804445a90093159ed9d254"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am your friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Exclamatory",
                "Interrogative"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2e7963c60a674e5dbc31960da706be45"
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister lives in Mexico.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Imperative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7f035ce2e189475ca6740346a628a69f"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did you do then?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Interrogative",
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6e34fe42c9fd45e2bf2d52b782f71616"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do be a bit more careful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5043cf9863244a91934731795ea462ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "Never speak to me like that again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0f9aec9b92554118839b943cb569ae08"
        },
        {
            "question": "Always remember what I told you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Exclamatory",
                "Interrogative"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81c7dcfa6f494de0ab564de1e795f2ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ball rolled slowly into the goal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory",
                "Imperative"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "59c9fd9657154045a8f8f9a82dd88dec"
        }
    ]
}